"I couldn't help myself, I couldn't please you have to understand   Ok, I did her...in a movie, a snuff film, but I'm not sorry.  Ok, I did her...in a movie, a snuff film, but I'm not sorry. I was set up... I didn't do anything. It was me... only it wasn't me. It was the booze... it takes me over. I'm sorry.. really i'm so sorry. I was set up... I didn't do anything. It was me... only it wasn't me. It was the booze... it takes me over. I'm sorry.. really i'm so sorry. I helped them, all of them. I took their pain away. I helped them, all of them. I took their pain away. We share the same dream. That's it We share the same dream. That's it We share the same dreams. That's it. We share the same dreams. That's it. Yes, I did it. Is that what you want to hear? Yes, I did it. Is that what you want to hear? Have you ever watched someone burn alive?  Have you ever watched someone burn alive?  I'll f**** you if you let me go.  I'll f**** you if you let me go.  None. Blamed the killings on mother issues  None. Blamed the killings on mother issues  You're the one that needs setting free, little brother. Your life is a lie. People you've been.... You're the one that needs setting free, little brother. Your life is a lie. People you've been.... Madolee curses you! Madolee curses you! You kill me, what do you leave behind?  You kill me, what do you leave behind?  She is not worth it, you're better of without that c***! She is not worth it, you're better of without that c***! I knew you weren't going to kill me. I knew you weren't going to kill me. I'll f******* kill you. I'll f******* kill you. Unknown. Unknown. Don't do this Don't do this Who are you? Who are you? Unknown Unknown no..last Sunday no...I was getting high with Sherry..or Carrie shes ah.. shes ah hell of a fÄ no..last Sunday no...I was getting high with Sherry..or Carrie shes ah.. shes ah hell of a fÄ ugh............. ugh............. Hey..ugh- Hey..ugh- No. You got me mixed up with somebody else. No. You got me mixed up with somebody else. You finally brought me the perfect pie and then,  You finally brought me the perfect pie and then,  What the ****? Who are you?  What the ****? Who are you?  You're a little freak! You think I'm done with you? You think this ends here? It doesnt! You're a little freak! You think I'm done with you? You think this ends here? It doesnt!  Let's hope your this talkative once I get my tools  Let's hope your this talkative once I get my tools  I know you  I know you You will choose your life over theirs You will choose your life over theirs  It's already over. Could you? Thank you.   It's already over. Could you? Thank you.  Well I'm sorry for your loss, But your dead wife can suck my ****! Well I'm sorry for your loss, But your dead wife can suck my ****! You don't know what you are getting into. You don't know what you are getting into. There gonna find you. You C*nt. There gonna find you. You C*nt. "